<mediawiki xml:lang="en"><page><title>Thread 19554306</title><revision><text>&lt;!-- Autogenerated by 4ch-to-mw.py --&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Deculture 1340192015 No.19554306&lt;/b&gt;
[[File:1340192015558.png|thumb|left|200x200px]]
&lt;pre style='font-family: sans-serif;'&gt;
You are a Magical GIrl.

In the past, you seem to have referred to yourself as Murderface.

Your memory isn't the best. You remember something things faintly, like viewing them through smoked glass. Others you remember startlingly clearly, as if you're there, watching them unfold, replaying over and over again.

One of them being shooting a smiling pink-haired girl in the face, moments after she tore your still-beating heart out from your chest with clawed hands.

You are Chiaki Matsuda, and you are in the seedy bar that's just a few blocks away from your own apartment.

You're not too sure how you ended up here.
&lt;/pre&gt;
----------------------------------
&lt;b&gt;Anonymous 1340192499 No.19554350&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;pre style='font-family: sans-serif;'&gt;
&gt;&gt;19554306
Check inventory, check physical condition, assess drunkenness, try to remember if we had a job to do, order another drink.
&lt;/pre&gt;
----------------------------------
&lt;b&gt;Deculture 1340192647 No.19554365&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;pre style='font-family: sans-serif;'&gt;
Well, you're not exactly sure, but you have an idea. After what had happened in Mami's apartment - and having spent a good chunk of the day helping her clean up - you had decided to step out for a moment. 

Maybe you didn't want to stick around too much. Sure, the food was good, and it felt nice to be around the blonde. But you didn't quite care for the company - namely, the blue-haired bitch glaring at you after every bite. Or the lectures that little rat bastard kept spouting.

You wanted some fresh air, and you ended up where you normally tried your level best to kill your liver.

It's funny how things work out.
&lt;/pre&gt;
----------------------------------
&lt;b&gt;Deculture 1340192987 No.19554396&lt;/b&gt;
[[File:1340192987122.png|thumb|left|200x200px]]
&lt;pre style='font-family: sans-serif;'&gt;
&gt;&gt;19554350

The bar doesn't really have a name. It's just a bar, built there to give people a place to try and drown whatever sorrows they have. It's staffed by a tall, dark-skinned man with the biggest afro you've ever seen, and sharp facial hair you swear is tailored to make his furious scowl look like it's taking up 90% of his face.

You check your inventory. Everything's pretty much there, same as the last time. Well, except the money. You already gave that to Charles, the Bartender.

Oh. You have that envelope Sayaka tossed your way. You haven't opened it yet. It's supposed to be your next assignment.

You're...well, you're not drunk. You could be drunk a bit more, though.
&lt;/pre&gt;
----------------------------------
&lt;b&gt;Anonymous 1340193113 No.19554408&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;pre style='font-family: sans-serif;'&gt;
&gt;&gt;19554396
Get another drink and make it a double, stuff two cigarettes in our mouth and light them up, head to a private table instead of the bar and open up the envelope.
&lt;/pre&gt;
----------------------------------
&lt;b&gt;Deculture 1340194121 No.19554505&lt;/b&gt;
[[File:1340194121906.png|thumb|left|200x200px]]
&lt;pre style='font-family: sans-serif;'&gt;
&gt;&gt;19554408

You've already drunk your money's worth, but you do have a tab, and Charles still owes you for that time when you solved a particularly nasty problem involving a couple of Yakuzas trying to shoot up the joint. You order a double whisky, and are mere seconds from lighting the cigarettes when you hear the bar doors open behind you, a cheerfully grating voice ringing out. 

"Hey! If it isn't ol' Murderface! Still trying to take yourself out the slow way, huh? Alcohol and pills?" The cigarettes end up on the bar, thankfully not into your double, as a hearty slap slams into your back with resounding force. "Heard you actually took out a Witch this time without killing anyone by accident! You're improving!"

Sakura Kyoko. This night just turned out a whole lot worse.

What is your reply?
&lt;/pre&gt;
----------------------------------
&lt;b&gt;Anonymous 1340194713 No.19554544&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;pre style='font-family: sans-serif;'&gt;
Offer her a cig and give her the assignment.
&lt;/pre&gt;
----------------------------------
&lt;b&gt;Deculture 1340195406 No.19554613&lt;/b&gt;
[[File:1340195406976.png|thumb|left|200x200px]]
&lt;pre style='font-family: sans-serif;'&gt;
Trying to look as if that slap hadn't almost knocked the lungs out of your body, you grab your glass and drain it of whisky, not caring if it burned like hell on the way down. Motioning to Charles for another refill, you place the cigarettes back into your mouth, lighting them simultaneously, before giving her the most withering look you could ever muster.

She only looks back at you, blankly, somewhat confused, and partly waiting for something to happen.

Grumbling about one-eyed idiots, you tuck the envelope underneath one arm and grab your drink. You slide off the bar stool and trod off to a private table at the corner, but to your increasing ire, she follows suit. Just like some sort of one-eyed puppy with a Pocky addiction.

"Well, I guess some things never change. You're still the most rousing conversation partner anyone could get." Kyoko chimes as she annoyingly seats herself from across you, waving at Charles and ordering her own drink. "Come on, don't be sulky. I came around to see how you were doing, after all! Isn't that what friends do?"

[]Kyoko, please, this is not the time.
[]Friends don't set other friends on fire.
[]Your girlfriend almost made a pincushion out my kidneys. Leave me to drink in peace.
&lt;/pre&gt;
----------------------------------
&lt;b&gt;Anonymous 1340195460 No.19554618&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;pre style='font-family: sans-serif;'&gt;
&gt;&gt;19554544
&gt;give her the assignment
Nonsense. As much as you'd love to pass your duties on someone else, you'd hate to miss a chance to get Grief Seed. 
They are the thing that keeps your clock ticking. Cigs, booze and pills are just oiling to make it tick smoother, but Seeds are the thing that really matters. That is, if anything does.
&lt;/pre&gt;
----------------------------------
&lt;b&gt;Anonymous 1340195540 No.19554625&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;pre style='font-family: sans-serif;'&gt;
&gt;&gt;19554613
&gt;[X]Your girlfriend almost made a pincushion out my kidneys. Leave me to drink in peace.
&lt;/pre&gt;
----------------------------------
&lt;b&gt;Anonymous 1340195814 No.19554651&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;pre style='font-family: sans-serif;'&gt;
&gt;&gt;19554618
Ah, I do not know how magical girls are powered here. That seems like a thing to do then.
&lt;/pre&gt;
----------------------------------
&lt;b&gt;Anonymous 1340196143 No.19554685&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;pre style='font-family: sans-serif;'&gt;
&gt;&gt;19554651
Basically Magical Girls get corruption over time and by using Magic, what you do is take a Grief Seed from a defeated Witch and shunt the corruption into their in order to extend your life.
&lt;/pre&gt;
----------------------------------
&lt;b&gt;Deculture 1340196600 No.19554729&lt;/b&gt;
[[File:1340196600348.png|thumb|left|200x200px]]
&lt;pre style='font-family: sans-serif;'&gt;
&gt;&gt;19554625

"W-what? My...my girlfriend? B-but I don't...o-oh, YOU MEAN SAYAKA, HAHAHA! OH, THAT'S RICH, MURDERFACE! WE'RE JUST GOOD FRIENDS, REALLY! AHAHAHA!"

The forced fake laughter would've been disturbing anyone else in the bar, if there had been anyone else in the damn bar besides you and Charles. After a few moments' more of fresh denial, she hunkers down and hisses at you, her one good eye glaring.

"I swear, Murderface, make a crack like that again and I'll ambush you myself one of these days." And then, like a switch had been flipped, she grins again just as the bartender brings her drink over. Some sort of red girly drink, you're not sure what it's exactly called. Smells a bit fruity, though.

"But, uh, sorry about that. We're kind of going through a rough patch." Kyoko says, managing to look sheepish as she cautiously sips her drink. You shoot her a look, shake your head, and make to open the envelope. You've ignored it long enough. 

"So, uh, what really happened? In Mami's apartment, I mean. One of the Kyuubeys said it was a particularly strong one. How'd you manage that?"

How do you reply?
&lt;/pre&gt;
----------------------------------
&lt;b&gt;Anonymous 1340196603 No.19554731&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;pre style='font-family: sans-serif;'&gt;
&gt;&gt;19554685
Some sort of arcane corruption, I assume, not just a penchant for booze and pocky?

This stuff about being set on fire wasn't in the previous thread, was it?
&lt;/pre&gt;
----------------------------------
&lt;b&gt;Anonymous 1340196889 No.19554760&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;pre style='font-family: sans-serif;'&gt;
&gt;&gt;19554731
Magic corruption, yeah.

&gt;&gt;19554729
The same way you kill any other witch, you cause enough brute trauma to a vulnerable location. 

It tried to interrupt my breakfast, and I do not take kindly to anyone getting between me and pancakes. 

Give her a cigarette and light up another one.
&lt;/pre&gt;
----------------------------------
&lt;b&gt;Anonymous 1340197070 No.19554777&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;pre style='font-family: sans-serif;'&gt;
&gt;&gt;19554729
You know QBs, always talk too much. That's the trait I really hate.

As for that thing in Mami's flat, was not really a Witch, just someone given "the kiss", it was too late to save her, so I had to do it the starighforward way. Shoot it 'til it died. Didn't even take that long, really.

How comes you are not chewing anything right now? You always do.
&lt;/pre&gt;
----------------------------------
&lt;b&gt;Deculture 1340197987 No.19554874&lt;/b&gt;
[[File:1340197987266.png|thumb|left|200x200px]]
&lt;pre style='font-family: sans-serif;'&gt;
&gt;&gt;19554760
&gt;&gt;19554777

"Huh. Nothing really special, then, I guess." It seems that she's strangely relieved about that, but with your odd one-eyed acquaintance, you can't be too sure. "That's pretty bad luck, though, having one pop up right there. When you're just about to arrive and all."

You glance up at her, before shaking your head again as you unravel the string lock on the envelope, sucking down greedily on the two cigarettes currently occupying your lips. 

After a moment of continuing to ruin your lungs and voice, you grumble out your question around your cigarettes, and the girl sitting in front of you reddens somewhat.

"Y-yeah, I guess. I've been trying to quit. Too much sweets and all, costume's getting a bit...tight. " It's then that she brightens up, again. "Hey, give me one of those things. They help make you lose weight, right?"

You shrug, and give her a cigarette from your box, letting her light it up with one of your already-spent ones. As she smokes her first cigarette - coughing and hacking loudly after the very first puff, you pull out the papers inside the envelope. There are two, with a photograph of what looks like a young female idol. You're not into that sort of music, but she does look stupid and two-dimensional enough to be one.

Kyuubey has loaned you out as security. Perfect.
&lt;/pre&gt;
----------------------------------
&lt;b&gt;Anonymous 1340198236 No.19554913&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;pre style='font-family: sans-serif;'&gt;
&gt;&gt;19554874
Fucking security detail. 

What are the details on the job? Who is after her? How long are we on security? Why the fuck should we care about what happens to her? Where are we protecting her, home, work, both? What enemies does she have?
&lt;/pre&gt;
----------------------------------
&lt;b&gt;Anonymous 1340198412 No.19554936&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;pre style='font-family: sans-serif;'&gt;
&gt;&gt;19554874
Just make up with your girlfriend. Then the weight will fall off, stress makes people fat after all

Read our instructions while she simultaneously ponders the effectiveness of our advice and gets mad at it
&lt;/pre&gt;
----------------------------------
&lt;b&gt;Deculture 1340199338 No.19555050&lt;/b&gt;
[[File:1340199338407.jpg|thumb|left|200x200px]]
&lt;pre style='font-family: sans-serif;'&gt;
&gt;&gt;19554936
&gt;&gt;19554913

"Huh? Really? W-well, I guess that sort of makes sense..." Kyoko's voice trails off as she thoughtfully nibbles on her cigarette's filter, not exactly breathing in the smoke. You ignore her and look at the assignment Kyuubey has already signed you up for in advance.

The client's name is Minase Iori. Age 16. Apparently, a group of otakus have declared their undying love for her, and had promised to take her away sometime before her upcoming concert. You've been contracted to assist as her personal security detail until she goes to America for the next stage of her world tour. It seems to be a lot of money, and Kyuubey had promised you two grief seeds in return for it.

Not the most challenging of jobs, you suppose. Just another babysitting job. Otakus aren't the most threatening sort, either. You'd think a normal security detail would have sufficed, but her studio seemed adamant that special measures were taken.

Of course, you know that whatever Kyuubey sends your way, it usually turns out to be more than you bargained for.

You're asked to report, as soon as you can, to the hotel where she's staying. You know where it is, and you can get there quickly enough.

"Huh. Babysitting job, huh? That sucks." Kyoko manages to blow smoke right into your face as she offers her unneeded opinion. "Yeah, good luck there. The guys you're watching out for are serious perverts."

[]Ask Kyoko more about these perverts.
[]Call Kyuubey and tell him to get you another assignment, this one reeks.
[]Get another drink before leaving for the hotel.
&lt;/pre&gt;
----------------------------------
&lt;b&gt;Anonymous 1340199486 No.19555069&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;pre style='font-family: sans-serif;'&gt;
&gt;&gt;19555050
Ask Kyoko about the perverts and acquire more booze
&lt;/pre&gt;
----------------------------------
&lt;b&gt;Anonymous 1340199510 No.19555075&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;pre style='font-family: sans-serif;'&gt;
&gt;&gt;19555050
[X]Ask Kyoko more about these perverts.

We need to know the threat these people pose, we're a professional.
&lt;/pre&gt;
----------------------------------
&lt;b&gt;Anonymous 1340200319 No.19555191&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;pre style='font-family: sans-serif;'&gt;
&gt;Ask about the perverts, and if she's one of them.
&lt;/pre&gt;
----------------------------------
&lt;b&gt;Deculture 1340201431 No.19555359&lt;/b&gt;
[[File:1340201431195.png|thumb|left|200x200px]]
&lt;pre style='font-family: sans-serif;'&gt;
&gt;&gt;19555191
&gt;&gt;19555075
&gt;&gt;19555069

Charles just places the bottle of whisky in front of you and leaves you to refill your glass at your own pace, just like every night. Kyoko frowns at your question and perhaps veiled insult, but seems to give it some serious thought (which is rare, considering she's now biting into cigarette filter like it's pocky).

"Well, one of her fellow idols got targeted last month by these losers, some girl named Yayoi or something or other. They didn't really think much about them, just put up the usual security detail, couple of armed gorillas in shades, you know what I mean."

She finally notices that she's chewing on filter, and hastily spits it out. "Bleah! Anyway, turns out they'd been planning it for the longest time. They disguised themselves as hotel staff and locked her in that very room. Security detail didn't even hear a peep out of that place, and you can bet they took their time with her. No one got caught, but the footage hit every pay for porn site there the night after." Kyoko shakes her head. "Girl went into hiding after that. Heard she went insane or somethin'."

Rapists. Wonderful, you think as you drain your third...or fourth glass, you can't remember. All you know is that you've dealt with such folk before, and you usually ended up wasting too much ammo.

"Well, are you gonna take it or what? I wouldn't." The eyepatched girl grumbles. "Two grief seeds, but then again, you're not exactly the type to play white knight. I mean, look at you." She laughs. "It's barely dinnertime and you already smell like booze."
&lt;/pre&gt;
----------------------------------
&lt;b&gt;Anonymous 1340201594 No.19555384&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;pre style='font-family: sans-serif;'&gt;
&gt;&gt;19555359
"Shooting rapists is a reward on itself"

"yeah, I'll take it"
&lt;/pre&gt;
----------------------------------
&lt;b&gt;Deculture 1340203405 No.19555685&lt;/b&gt;
[[File:1340203405275.png|thumb|left|200x200px]]
&lt;pre style='font-family: sans-serif;'&gt;
&gt;&gt;19555384

Kyoko blinks at your reply, before grinning. "Yeah, things never do change. I knew you'd say that, even though this isn't really your type of thing." Stubbing out her cigarette on the table as she sips her drink. "At least this way something exciting'll be in the news. Hey, you think you can execute one of them on camera? That's always good TV, you know. Gives us a bit more exposure."

You start to reply that you'd think about it, but it's then that you freeze as you see Kyoko's face blur in front of you. Not a migraine, she's not going in and out of focus, and it's certainly not your glasses, either. And you're not quite that drunk. Not yet. It must be...it must be...

You stare as Kyoko is suddenly replaced by a hallucination. The pink-haired girl in your dreams. The one that you shot right in the face, just before she tore your still-beating heart out of your chest with her bare hands.

"Hello, Homura-chan." She says, beaming. Her voice, like Kyuubey's, bypasses your ears, heard directly in your mind. Her lips aren't even moving.

You're not Homura. You're Chiaki. Chiaki Matsuda.

How do you react?
&lt;/pre&gt;
----------------------------------
&lt;b&gt;Anonymous 1340204258 No.19555818&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;pre style='font-family: sans-serif;'&gt;
&gt;&gt;19555685

"Do you know why I drink?", take a shot, "Some people drink to remember, but not me. I drink to forget. And it works. I've forgotten my name, the day of the week, the faces of my parents, even what I did last night. But you? Your stupid face? The thing that drove me to the bottle in the first place? Clear as crystal, every fucking time.

What do you want."
&lt;/pre&gt;
----------------------------------
&lt;b&gt;Deculture 1340205498 No.19556039&lt;/b&gt;
[[File:1340205498132.png|thumb|left|200x200px]]
&lt;pre style='font-family: sans-serif;'&gt;
&gt;&gt;19555818

Despite the horror of something from your recurring nightmares coming out into reality and actually talking to you, you manage to say this perfectly, even managing not to spill any whisky down the front of your costume as you drain your glass.

The illusion's smiles merely grow wider as she opens her eyes. Revealing two orbs of pure midnight black, as if her irises had bled out to her sclera in the most horrible way possible.

"Of course your memory's going to be unreliable. Fakes will never be as good as the original, so a few flaws here and there are going to be par for the course. But at the very least, you still remember how to slowly self-destruct. That's something the original was very good at."

She lets out a sigh, and you smell her breath, pungent and sweet with decay and corruption.

"I'm just here to wish you good luck. You have a thirty percent chance of dying on this particular undertaking. Try not to get yourself killed too early, Homura-chan. I mean, I want a rematch, but I'm in no hurry. I like it better when you die slowly."

[] Bullshit. You're just another hallucination. I haven't been sleeping right. Besides, I killed you. You're already dead.
[] No. Let's go right now. You, me, outside.
&lt;/pre&gt;
----------------------------------
&lt;b&gt;Anonymous 1340223515 No.19557337&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;pre style='font-family: sans-serif;'&gt;
&gt;&gt;19556039
&gt;[X] Bullshit. You're just another hallucination. I haven't been sleeping right. Besides, I killed you. You're already dead.

"You died a long time ago. You not a Ghost. You're not even a memory. A memory of a memory. And a bad one at that. 
She would have never said something like that."

Also: 
Music for that scene: 
http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=AsbzP1AVS4k&amp;feature=relmfu
&lt;/pre&gt;
----------------------------------
&lt;b&gt;Deculture 1340233884 No.19559357&lt;/b&gt;
[[File:1340233884824.png|thumb|left|200x200px]]
&lt;pre style='font-family: sans-serif;'&gt;
&gt;&gt;19557337

The phantasm seems to slightly frown at your words, brow quirking as if this reaction was entirely unexpected - but her expression smoothens out to her previous one, her dark eyes glittering. It's then that she leans forward, smiling once more, her small tongue darting out to lick her lips.

"Maybe, Homura-chan. But I can still kill you." 

And it's then that you feel it. Crippling, numbing pain, crunching into sensation at the back of your head and then stabbing forward. You grasp at your own head, fingers curling into your hair, as you grit your teeth against the pain. It's familiar, but at the same time something you had hoped never to experience again.

"Hey. Hey! Murderface! MURDERFACE!"

And as suddenly as it came, as soon as you hear Kyoko's voice over the sharp whine ringing in your ears - the pain disappears, taking with it the hallucination. You look up, cautiously, to check if Kyoko is still her ugly, one-eyed self.

She is. For the first time, you seem particularly relieved to see her.

There's a first time for everything, you suppose.

"Hey, hey, you alright? Come on, Murderface, don't scare me like that." Kyoko amusingly almost seems concerned about you. "Look, I-I don't know what sort of shit you're taking, but you gotta cut down. Really. Maybe we can even get you some of them patches for the smokes--"

You shrug her off, murmur an apology, and frown as you realize that you've knocked the whisky bottle off the table and into the floor in this particular episode. You glance apologetically at Charles, and he merely nods. It'll be on your tab.
&lt;/pre&gt;
----------------------------------
&lt;b&gt;Deculture 1340234377 No.19559447&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;pre style='font-family: sans-serif;'&gt;
You murmur something to Kyoko and make to leave, but she grabs your hand.

"Murderface? Murderface, talk to me. What the hell was that about? What happened there?"

You remind her, as politely as you can, that you have a name and it's Chiaki Matsuda.

"I don't give a shit! What was that?! Why did you suddenly blank out on me and started growling all of that strange stuff?! Whatever you're taking, you have to cut down. It's not good."

You're fine. ...Wait, what did she say? You ask her what you said.

"...Something about...something about 'the flesh of fallen angels'. Y-yeah. I mean, I've heard weirder from you, but..."

You stare at her, suddenly feeling cold, and it's then that you roughly pull your hand out of her grasp, grabbing the assignment papers with your other and making to leave.

This shit, you remind yourself, is why you work alone.

And you've apparently just confirmed that God exists, and she wants you dead.

"M-Murderface...? Murderface, get the fuck back here! That is some crazy shit, and--" Kyoko's voice rises the moment you step through the bar doors. "GOD DAMMIT! YOU ALWAYS DO THIS! ALRIGHT, FINE! SEE IF I CARE! SEE IF ANYONE CARES, MURDERFACE! YOU'LL GET YOURSELF KILLED AND EVERYONE YOU LOVE WITH THAT KIND OF ATTITUDE!"

As if you needed reminding.

You stomp off towards the direction you remember that particular Hotel is. Time to get to that job.

==

Sorry about my absence, everyone. The cloudflare issues kinda stopped me from updating. I wanted to end it neatly here, though, so the next thread will be able to start better. It'll be at the same time.

Thank you for everyone who participated.
&lt;/pre&gt;
----------------------------------
</text></revision></page></mediawiki>